[
    {"question": "Who fell down the stairs in LT17 during THAR?", "answer": "Shao Lun"},
    {"question": "Who is the 36th JCRC President?", "answer": "Wei Xuan"},
    {"question": "Which committee cried during DND 23/24?", "answer": "Hall Affairs Board"},
    {"question": "Which block had their lounge dirtied during OC 24/25?", "answer": "D Block"},
    {"question": "How many sports are there in TH?", "answer": "30"},
    {"question": "Which team got fourth place in IHG 23/24?", "answer": "Floorball F"},
    {"question": "Which team got fourth place in IHG 24/25?", "answer": "Road Relay M"},
    {"question": "What is the exact name of DC's JBL speaker?", "answer": "JBL Partybox"},
    {"question": "Which block should have been bombed this year?", "answer": "A Block"},
    {"question": "What was gamified to gain votes for TH STHar Awards?", "answer": "Ramadan"},
    {"question": "Which block cheated during Walk for Rice 24/25 but still lost?", "answer": "D Block"},
    {"question": "Who promised their entire committee black jerseys?", "answer": "Kieran Phoon"},
    {"question": "What is the full name of A Block's Resident Fellow?", "answer": "Natalie Wong"},
    {"question": "What is the full name of B Block's Resident Fellow?", "answer": "Shaun Kang"},
    {"question": "What is the full name of C Block's Resident Fellow?", "answer": "Professor Tan Swee Ching"},
    {"question": "What is the full name of D Block's Resident Fellow?", "answer": "Professor Hans Tan"},
    {"question": "What is the full name of E Block's Resident Fellow?", "answer": "Doreen Tan"},
    {"question": "Which day of the week would you see waffles for CH breakfast?", "answer": "Wednesday"},
    {"question": "How many residents are there in Temasek Hall?", "answer": "485"},
    {"question": "What is the name on the Comm Hall Uncle's cap?", "answer": "Betty"},
    {"question": "Who did Tricia Sim hug in VPU's Short Film Competition video?", "answer": "Keith Loh"}
]
